<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>ツール &#8211; JEDA</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.eosjapan.org/?feed=rss2&#038;cat=6" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.eosjapan.org</link>
	<description>一般社団法人　日本EOS ​開発者協会</description>
	<lastBuildDate>
	Tue, 19 Feb 2019 05:29:33 +0000	</lastBuildDate>
	<language>ja</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.eosjapan.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/cropped-logo-1-32x32.png</url>
	<title>ツール &#8211; JEDA</title>
	<link>https://www.eosjapan.org</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>JEDA Partners with Infinito Wallet, the World-Leading Universal Wallet!</title>
		<link>https://www.eosjapan.org/?p=594</link>
				<comments>https://www.eosjapan.org/?p=594#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 05:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jill]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[ツール]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.eosjapan.org/?p=594</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[JEDA (Japan EOS Developer Asso ...]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://www.eosjapan.org/">JEDA (Japan EOS Developer Association),</a>is honored to announce our partnership with&nbsp;<a href="https://www.infinitowallet.io/">Infinito Wallet</a>. Through this technology collaboration, JEDA and Infinito Wallet, will bring greater value not only to our respective communities but also for the global EOS community as a whole.&nbsp;We plan to build brand credibility and branding to further spread global adoption of EOS blockchain and its various unique technologies.</p>



<p>JEDA is committed to promoting EOS in Japan and organizing developers to build the EOS ecosystem. As development is an important cycle of EOS ecosystem, JEDA strongly supports the financial side for DApp developers for smooth development. JEDA also conducts educational activities to increase knowledge and improve blockchain skill set for EOS communities throughout the country by holding technician meet-ups and public meetups.</p>



<p><a href="https://www.infinitowallet.io/">Infinito Wallet</a>&nbsp;is a world-leading Universal Wallet, home to the widest range of leading cryptocurrencies and blockchain services for crypto enthusiast worldwide. It is globally acclaimed as one of, if not,&nbsp;the best crypto wallet for EOS on the market. Recently, we launched an in-wallet&nbsp;<a href="https://www.infinitowallet.io/app-square-is-here-enjoy-all-innovative-blockchain-dapps-on-infinito-wallet/">DApp browser, App Square</a>, where users can access a wide variety of innovative daily blockchain services. With this, Infinito Wallet is now a one-stop gateway solution with all applications and services for all crypto consumer needs.&nbsp;</p>



<p><strong>JEDA x Infinito: Joining hands for the benefit of global EOS community.&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>With this collaboration, JEDA will provide Infinito Wallet with support&nbsp;for integration of EOS DApps on App Square. At the moment, Infinito team is focusing our effort on supporting community-favourite EOS DApps and we hope to enable this highly demanded feature for users with this partnership.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Moreover, JEDA will assist Infinito Wallet with integrating more advanced EOS features including&nbsp;EOS account self-registration&nbsp;and&nbsp;EOS Block Producers voting. Infinito Wallet has always been recognized as the best wallet for EOS users thanks to our comprehensive&nbsp;<a href="https://www.infinitowallet.io/?s=EOS&amp;lang=en">support for EOS</a>&nbsp;including: support for all EOS tokens, stake/unstake NET and CPU bandwidth, buy/ sell RAM, import/export EOS private keys, and&nbsp;<a href="https://www.infinitowallet.io/tag/communityoffer/">free EOS account registration campaign</a>&nbsp;with EOS community partners. Through this partnership, crypto users will be able to fully utilize all unique functions and innovative applications of EOS blockchain inside one Universal Wallet.</p>



<p><strong>From JEDA’s side, Co-founder Jacky Zhang says:&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>“We are very happy to form a partnership with Infinito Wallet, the universal gateway to blockchain services, especially when we learned that Infinito Wallet pays special attention to the Japanese market. After that, we will work together to promote EOS and DApps in the Japanese market to serve more Japanese users.”</p>



<p><strong>On this partnership milestone, Infinito Wallet’s CEO, Mr. Junya Yamamoto, says:</strong></p>



<p>“It is our honor to collaborate with the EOS Block Producer from Japan, JEDA. Infinito Wallet and JEDA will work together to bring great benefits to EOS communities worldwide. We aim to provide users with a truly universal gateway to all the advanced features and game-changing applications on EOS blockchain on Infinito Wallet”&nbsp;</p>



<p><strong>About JEDA</strong></p>



<p><a href="https://www.eosjapan.org/">JEDA (Japan EOS Developer Association)</a>&nbsp;supports the development of the EOS ecosystem in Japan with the goal to establish an ecosystem on EOS, propose online and offline EOS events to gather EOS enthusiast and developers, and develop engaging EOS DApps as well as multiple services based on EOS blockchainGet Infinito Wallet Now!</p>



<p>Follow JEDA</p>



<p> Homepage http://www.eosjapan.org<br> Facebook https://www.facebook.com/eosjapan/<br> Twitter https://twitter.com/eosjapan_jeda<br> Instagram https://www.instagram.com/eosjapan/<br> Telegram https://t.me/eosjapan</p>



<p><strong>About Infinito Wallet</strong></p>



<p>Positioning as a leading universal wallet for crypto users,&nbsp;<a href="https://www.infinitowallet.io/">Infinito Wallet</a>&nbsp;serves as a gateway for users to maximize usage and potentials of their cryptocurrencies.&nbsp;Our DApp browser, App Square, provides access to the most innovative blockchain applications for daily user needs.&nbsp;&nbsp;By selectively expanding our partner network, Infinito Wallet aims to build an ecosystem of practical blockchain services including exchanges, ID/KYC solutions, and other blockchain-related business services. At the same time, we support communities of developers and businesses with Infinito Blockchain Platform, an open blockchain infrastructure of technologies and compliant-ready services, so that they can seamlessly build, launch, and operate innovative products and services efficiently.</p>



<p>Infinito Wallet’s core development team of blockchain R&amp;D experts has intensive professional experience. Currently, our organization has more than 300 members including developers, designers, business, marketing, and customer service specialists. We are promoting research on infrastructure for cryptocurrencies and development utilizing blockchain.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://www.eosjapan.org/?feed=rss2&#038;p=594</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOSにはTokenPocket Walletを利用しましょう</title>
		<link>https://www.eosjapan.org/?p=400</link>
				<comments>https://www.eosjapan.org/?p=400#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 11:07:03 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mariko]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[ツール]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.eosjapan.info/?p=400</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[TokenPocketはモバイルライトウォレットアプリです。 ...]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><span class="s1">TokenPocket</span>はモバイルライトウォレットアプリです。</p>
<p class="p1">安全で厳重に保管され、使いやすく、そして処理能力の高いデジタル資産ウォレットアプリケーションを一般ユーザーに提供するように設計されています。</p>
<p class="p1">非常にスムーズな使用感で、国内ユーザーの使用習慣に適しています。 初心者向きです。</p>
<p class="p1">さらにこのウォレットはマルチシステムのデジタル資産を統合し、特に<span class="s1">EOS</span>を選択して保存することができます。</p>
<p class="p1">今すぐ投票して、ここで<span class="s1">RAM</span>を交換しましょう。超高速体験。</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1">将来的にウォレットの中でもサポート可能なクロスチェーン取引は、（実際のクロスチェーン原子取引）デジタル資産の保存と流通におけるユーザーの利便性を最大限に高めます。</p>
<p class="p1">我々は<span class="s1">TokenPocket</span>チームと協力して、近々日本語版も提供します。</p>
<p class="p1">ぜひ楽しんでみてくださいね</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1">現在<span class="s1">Android</span>と<span class="s1">iOS</span>をサポートしています。ダウンロードはこちらからどうぞ：</p>
<p class="p3"><a href="https://www.mytokenpocket.vip">https://www.mytokenpocket.vip</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://www.eosjapan.org/?feed=rss2&#038;p=400</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
